jlabaudio.com 2008-02-20

# iPod nano Portable Speakers, USB Laptop Portable Speakers, Earbuds for iPod, Creative Zen, nano, Zune, Sansa, Laptops, Notebooks

JLab Audio Privacy Notice

» Introduction  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

» The Information We Collect  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the JLab Audio website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

* Name  
* Address  
* E-Mail Address  
* Phone Number  
* Credit/Debit Card Information

» The Way We Use Information  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

* We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.  
* We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  
* You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our Web site will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.  
* Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

» Our Commitment to Data Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

» Thank You  
Thank you for taking the time to read our privacy policy. Our staff at JLab Audio wishes you a great shopping experience. If you have questions please do not hesitate to contact us.
